var myQuestions = [
	{
		question: " The instruction format register to register has a length of",
		answers: {
			a: '2 bytes',
			b: '1 byte',
			c: '3 bytes',
                        d: '4 bytes'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'b'
	},
	{
		question: "The bit which is used by the REP instruction is",
		answers: {
			a: ' W-bit',
			b: 'S-bit',
			c: 'V-bit',
                        d: 'Z-bit'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'd'
	},
{
		question: "If a W-bit value is 1 then the operand is of",
		answers: {
			a: '8 bits',
			b: '4 bits',
			c: '16 bits',
                        d: '2 bits'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'c'
	},
{
		question: "The instructions which after execution transfer control to the next instruction in the sequence are called ",
		answers: {
			a: 'Sequential control flow instructions',
			b: 'control transfer instructions',
			c: 'Sequential control flow & control transfer instructions',
                        d: 'none of the mentioned'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'a'
	},
{
		question: "The instructions that transfer the control to some predefined address or the address specified in the instruction are called as",
		answers: {
			a: 'Sequential control flow instructions',
			b: 'control transfer instructions',
			c: 'Sequential control flow & control transfer instructions',
                        d: 'none of the mentioned'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'b'
	},
{
		question: "The instruction JUMP belongs to",
		answers: {
			a: 'sequential control flow instructions',
			b: 'control transfer instructions',
			c: 'branch instructions',
                        d: 'control transfer & branch instructions'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'd'
	},
{
		question: "The instruction, MOV AX, 0005H belongs to the address mode",
		answers: {
			a: 'register',
			b: 'direct',
			c: 'immediate',
                        d: 'register relative'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'c'
	},
{
		question: "The instruction, MOV AX, [2500H] is an example of",
		answers: {
			a: 'immediate addressing mode',
			b: 'direct addressing mode',
			c: 'indirect addressing mode',
                        d: 'register addressing mode'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'b'
	},
{
		question: "The contents of a base register are added to the contents of index register in ",
		answers: {
			a: 'indexed addressing mode',
			b: 'based indexed addressing mode',
			c: 'relative based indexed addressing mode',
                        d: 'based indexed and relative based indexed addressing mode'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'd'
	},
{
		question: "Which of the following is not a data copy/transfer instruction?",
		answers: {
			a: 'MOV',
			b: 'PUSH',
			c: 'DAS',
                        d: 'POP'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'c'
	}
];